Hated everyone.
And welcome to the front and double dip or boot camp.
So you're already into the course or maybe you are looking just at the free preview to see and check
out what are the projects that we are going to build up.
So the good news is we are going to build a whole lot of projects.
But before I show you all of the projects that we are going to work up and code along in this entire
coast Let me just be clear on one point that these are not only the projects which on which we are going
to be working.
There are a whole set of other projects which we haven't taken into account because they are small and
we just don't want to bother about them.
But yes we do have many other projects as well.
OK.
So in case you're wondering why I'm looking at the very top out there the screen is gigantic and camera
is long at the top.
So before further ado let me talk about these projects that we are going to work up.
And these are really good.
And in this whole package where we're going to start with HDMI elsea says this is a step by step process
out there so HD is says bootstrap javascript J.A.G. and finally project.
Everything is going to be in the steps.
But on every step we are going to just test those skills by designing a project out there.
So let's just talk about that.
So here you can see the very first project that we are going to build up is Fitow for Jim.
So this is the gym coming soon template and it looks really it looks really great.
And this is going to be your first project out there and again remember that this is irresponsive right
now.
We just try to make it.
And this is a pure HVM and nothing else.
And thereafter we will move ahead and talk about these kinds of things as well.
So this is a sushi restaurant coming soon template with this template utilizes the extremal five things
about the videos and there is a back end video as well.
Again everything is again responsive without using any of the Wordpress are any but any things like
bootstrap and things like that.
But again it's really good.
So this is going to be project number two and there is a whole lot of separate movies dedicated with
the name of the project that you can check out for these.
And thereafter we are going to build a tacky truck non-responsive Web site in order to get an idea how
responsive are good and how easy it is nowadays to code at a sponsored web site.
We're going to talk about how the non-responsive upside used to look like and still there are a lot
of corporate sectors and a lot of companies who are still having these Web sites just like this.
So we're going to talk about this again just as I togged this is non-responses so doesn't respond to
the my size out there.
So this is one part.
OK.
Taqi truck is good and there are a couple of challenges in the truck as well to make sure that you understand
how the templates are being edited.
One of the most important part of your day to day life job as the front end of our build up here will
be to edit the templates for the clients or maybe for your company.
So we'll be tackling that as well.
Further we will be moving on the To Do list app on this To-Do list app is actually built totally in
the CSX and the HDMI.
Nothing no jealousy at all but still look at this.
This goes out there and everything is being scratched and Maag and great but again everything is being
done in HD.
Mullins see SS moving further on we are going to build up this technical landing page and this is responsive
and a lot of things are happening here.
And we will also learn how the media query works out there.
So notice as this blue bar out there is going to turn into the green.
So there we go.
And there we go it turns into the green and here we are going to learn about the media queries how the
media queries are responsible for a completely different CSSA So there we go we are going to talk about
this.
And in case you haven't noticed look at the top menu bar the hamburger bar appears out there.
And there we go.
And one more thing in this we are going to do is we are going to look up for how these buttons are being
placed.
So these Facebook and Twitter button are also being policed as a project out there.
So we are going to talk about that as well in a separate project and we have many projects you might
see out there.
And thereafter we are going to move on to a completely different web page project and its a complete
full fledged application that you can utilize for maybe your client or your personal use.
And I think all of these project in these into our course along with images do come with a license of
feel free whatever you want to do with that.
Even commercially non-commercially whatever you want to fish in case you haven't noticed.
Let me just reload and watch this boy's photo out there.
It's a wobbly wobbly photo.
So we're going to learn how we can.
And he made these things and can apply these kinds of cool effects now after this section we have a
very good navigation section image and some content.
Again content image image content.
So we'll be flipping that all and we'll see how the editors help us to just copy and paste and replace
the things out there so this is really great after that try to sell the Yahoo.
I know it's already being sold but still we're going to try with this.
Nobody is going to buy Yahoo with this page.
But these bage are really popular as a landing page.
So what you can do you can just buy today selling some items put some items or images out there and
people can buy from these kinds of landing pages.
So this is really essential for every front end developer for their moving.
We do have an admin dashboard Yes.
Admin do have front ends as well.
Later on we are people just move out there and put some BHB maybe know Jesus or javascript's and things
like that onto these templates but his admin dashboard are also a part of a front end development so
people like to just give it as it go.
So there we go.
We do have a simple template of that dashboard notice all the font icons font or some icons are being
placed out there and add users categories.
These labels some bars out there many bar side bars and the table is there the detail table which is
usually populated by the HB or some backend scripts.
But this is just different and moving further.
We do have a random parser generator.
So by now you might have already learned the javascript and thereafter we're going to learn about these
things.
So this is a random password generator do you just enter whatever the length of the password you need.
Let's just say 8 click on the generate password every time it just generates a random password.
So we're going to have a look on how these things works and look how cool it is looking.
And after that we are going to move on to our simple clock ticking clock which is actually looks really
boring but it's really impressive.
The background color of the page actually changes based on the time.
So these are the hex values so R G B.
If I'll stay on this page for a few seconds you will notice this now that the colors do change slightly
or so we will learn how we can tackle that and this clock just sticks out and doesn't consume much of
the memory out there as well.
Finally let's move on to this guy and and thereafter we learn some of the queer defects as well.
So after learning that Jake really we'll be talking here as well.
So you will learn how this effect is being applied so you can just place two images under there can
be a slight it out there of seeing the effect before and after a lot of people do are restoring works
out there making all things good and are dead.
So recently I happened to tackle these kinds of projects and I've found this crazy plug in.
And we will learn how we can utilize that and we will learn how we can do that.
So previously it looked like that.
And then we made it look like that.
So these kinds of things are really handy out there.
Thereafter we will move on and look for the type ahead.
Now you might have seen that in Google or maybe in the twitter or everything.
So let's just say this is a state of USA.
And again notice there's a challenge here for the student as well.
So let say I am looking for the New York or something.
So as I type the new so New Jersey New Mexico is also being suggested as the as I type.
And again as I move to the lead just say I'm moving for the Arizona as I type A are automatically based
on that the search is being modified so charm of J queries being implemented here.
And the challenge here is really simple for the students.
But we'll talk about that challenge later on.
OK.
And finally a final project that will be building up is going to be this Bristowe coffee and it will
implement all of the things HVM bootstraps see javascript.
Jake ready animations parallax pretty much everything that we have learned is going to be implemented
here.
And we can see that this Bristo coffee is keep jumping but do notice this and a little more some time
button as I reload this get severe believably effect out there as well.
So this is what we're going to be doing some servers section three columns here.
And then the portfolio Web site some nice neat images are being placed here.
And artists do notice the parallax effect that we have implemented here.
This is a parallax effect and Feliks is so easy to implement out there and we're going to talk about
that as well.
Here we have implemented that do not is this be a part of our team again.
Wibbly Wobbly the kind of effect that we will implement are there and some amazing team we do have Mark
John and Peter three little kids doing a lot of jobs.
Wibbly Wobbly here and there and we're going to learn and they're off to notice the Perlitz and the
some code would look great here.
Very tiny but still giving a little glance too over perfection out there.
I noticed this is a parallax effect.
And there we go finally we have a contact form are there and all of these images and pretty much everything
are just open source so just feel free to do whatever you want to do with them.
So these are all the project overview that we are going to building up and all these projects are going
to get started from the very scratch.
No problem at all.
Not be copy and pasting the code.
I'll be writing what's in front of you.
But again everything is being polished.
You will not see any blunders or things like that or Sanaz and a lot of hours are thinking's nothing
that.
And let's just go ahead and try to make these projects once we take out the theoretical part and some
writing code challenges as well.
So see are there in the next movie.